it's hard but it does get
better Superman I had this discussion uh
last week the reason Superman we value
Superman or those Superman stories isn't
because he's always 100% with his s on
his uh chest and he's flying it's
because when he's down on Earth he works
in a newspaper organization he's a human
he's scared to ask the girl out at at
his office he he shared his his
vulnerabilities and then we get to
connect with him and say oh he's one of
us first and because we know he's one of
us he can now we can we can now can show
us his Superman powers I actually before
was before we got on this call I wanted
to get a quote that I saw that Clark
Kent said he said Clark Kent in the
movie said we all have something that
that we think we need to hide it's hard
but it does get better see he was able
to become Superman because he knew he
had to struggle first right we are all
superheroes we all have capes but when
we show our struggles when we show our
journey with people they get to see the
superhero inside right another quote
that I wanted to say uh this is Clark
Kent as well oftentimes a crisis has a
way of revealing a person's true nature
For Better or For Worse right he decided
to use his struggles to help people
right that's what he did and I decided
to use my struggles for the same way I
decided to make my my relationship with
my wife better as best as I could now
that I have a daughter I I share her the
struggles that I went through when I was
younger so I can have a better
relationship with her and now I went on
your uh Facebook group and I helped
others and then one day I reached out to
you and said I'd love to do a podcast
and now I'm here nine years later on
another podcast still doing the same
thing right I did it when I was
struggling and I'm doing it still in my
journey N9 years later still helping
others right but I didn't help others
until I was able to help myself until I
was able to slow down
enough to be able to see that I'm going
to be okay and that in my struggle I can
still work on myself I can still take
one step at a time I can still do just
the next step I don't have to know what
happens to me 5 years from now whether
I'm going to be cured whether I'm going
to be helped I just need to do the first
positive thing that's available to me
and if your first possible available
thing for you right now is the fact that
you clicked on this video and you're
listening to it
openhearted that's a win the fact that
you said in your struggle you know what
I still have the
capacity to go on YouTube and look for
something positive to listen to you're
already doing it because if you say to
me oh no I don't know if I can do it
you're listening right now and I hope
you're hearing this message loud and
clear